(gentle guitar music)
♪ I looked out this morning
and the sun was gone ♪
♪ Turned on some music to start my day ♪
♪ I lost myself in a familiar song ♪
♪ I closed my eyes and I slipped away ♪
(lively rock music)
♪ It's more than a feeling ♪
♪ More than a feeling ♪
♪ When I hear that old
song they used to play ♪
♪ More than a feeling ♪
♪ And I begin dreaming ♪
♪ 'Til I see Marianne walk away ♪
♪ I see my Marianne walking away ♪
(lively rock music)
(gentle guitar music)
♪ When I'm tired and thinking cold ♪
♪ I hide in my music, forget the day ♪
♪ And dream of a girl I used to know ♪
♪ I closed my eyes and she slipped away ♪
(lively rock music)
♪ She slipped away ♪
♪ It's more than a feeling ♪
♪ More than a feeling ♪
♪ When I hear that old
song they used to play ♪
♪ More than a feeling ♪
♪ And I begin dreaming ♪
♪ 'Til I see Marianne walk away ♪
(lively rock music)